http://somepage.com/privacy

Somepage.com Privacy Policy
We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we
will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not
identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about
your visit:
The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or
"yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that
is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website;
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
The date and time you access our site;
The pages you visit; and
If you linked to the website from another website, the address of that website.
We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors -- to learn about the number of
visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information
about individuals and their visits.
Voluntary User Registration
If you register you will be voluntarily providing personally identifiable information. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, we ask that you please do not provide the requested information. You may nevertheless continue to use most of our web site, subject, however, to the collection of information through cookies and log files as discussed above. If you have previously provided personally identifiable information by registration through our web site, you may request to be removed from our active database.
We do not, and will not, disclose, sell, rent or share any personally identifiable information received as a result of enrollment, registrations or e-commerce transactions on our web site with any third parties.
Links: Our Web sites may contain links to external Web sites that are not within our control. If you decide to use any of these external links, you will be connected to a site not covered by our privacy policies. We recommend that you read their privacy statements, since they may differ from ours. This privacy statement applies only to information collected on this web site.
Third Party Advertising
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you
visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name,
address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web
sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods
and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information
about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used
by these companies, please click here
http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp
Third Party Cookies
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
